you stop?
Shut it up!
WaaaaaaaAAAAH.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH.
Ufff...the whole island
floating in the sky.
This is like a dream.
no...
A NIGHMARE!
How can we hope it to be Kaido
His strength is too great!
What?
Why are you here?
No way!
Marco the Phoenix!
We need a lot of fire now!
Easy enough.
In that case, here you go.
What are you doing?
Oh, no, it's hot!
It's so hot!
I'm burning from the inside out!
Damn it!
Is this some kind of joke to you?
Thought you were an ally,
and this is what you do?
Explain yourself, or die!
Boy, somebody has a real short fuse.
All right, don't worry, Chopper.
I'll put it out for you.
Oh, my arm bones! I'm burning!
Or not.
Well, this is unique.
It's all right, my friend.
Relax.
But the fire!
Oh, wait.
Uh, I'm not burning.
I'm totally okay.
It's warm and comfy like
a perfect summer day.
It feels so nice. Dr. Chopper!
We're ready to begin
production of the antibodies.
If you girl would come this way!
Oh, my goodness!
It's a swarm of ice, Oni!
Miyagi, Tristan, run for it, hurry!
Might as well get them all, I guess.
Phoenix Pyrapples!
Wait, this is kind of nice, actually.
I can feel the chill melting away already.
Ah!
What was I doing?
Are you alright?
You had me worried there, but it
seems you came to your senses.
You sure scared me!
That's nice, but only thing I did
was raise their body temperature.
The second their stamina runs out, they'll
start going berserk just like before.
So you better use the time
while you've still got it.
You're a lifesaver!
A little time is all I needed.
Tristan! Miyagi!
You okay over there?
Yes, it seems.
Just shaking up is all. All right, then.
Let's get down to it.
Since we're clear for now,
we'll get right to work.
Thanks a bunch.
Guess they're using space in that tower.
Okay?
I'll kill you.
stupid bird and stupid raccoon playing
doctor and messing up all my stuff.
hey, you morons!
you don't really think he's gonna
spare his own enemies, do you?
he's gonna save his buddies and
they're gonna finish you off.
i don't know, our friends
are gonna die, that's right.
they'll die.
then you're all gonna
die unless you get rid of
that pest and bring back
my antibody immediately.
Simple enough.
I can lend a hand without much effort,
but it seems like we're overstaffed.
Roronoa, listen up.
I think you might be better off
fighting Kaido on the roof right now.
Having trouble getting up there?
Why not let me fly you then?
You Straw Hats are way too strong to
be dealing with a bunch of small fries.
But we can't leave yet.
We still have to protect Chopper.
It's fine, Mr.
Skeleton We can handle this We
won't let any harm come to Mr.
Raccoon You have my word.
Let's give it our best.
We've got this.
Hold up.
I'm not done with you yet.
A poo.
Check it!
You punks better give me
back that antibody or else!
They'll kill me if I don't get it!
I can't lose now!
I'm fighting for my life, dammit!
Oh, seriously?
Very well.
Have at you.
One more enemy.
Then we'll be on our way.
Flee to the tower, Mr. Raccoon!
We're all right!
Nooo!
Nooooo! Nooooo!
That's new.
He betrayed us?
So does that mean we should
attack him to protect Apoo?
Noooo!
Noooo! Noooo!
That's new.
Roronoa Zoro, if you can trust me as your
ally, let me handle this and go ahead.
Well, if nothing else,
it looks like you've got a knack
for betting on the right horse.
Hey, Saji!
Where are you?
If I had to guess,
I'd wager that he sensed
a powerful enemy nearby,
and he's holding them
off on the third floor.
I didn't think of that.
Guess my observation hockey's still weak.
He can't be far from here, but
I can't sense Sanji at all!
Do you feel something just now, enemies?
Indeed.
Many of them.
Nearby, ready to strike.
It seems they're quite formidable as well.
One of us is going to have to stay
behind and keep these foes occupied.
You go on ahead.
I'll draw their attention.
Up and load!
General...
Launcher!
Now that is how you make a mess of things!
CENRAL TANON!
Damn it! Get back!
Huh?
You think I'm just gonna
let you blow everything up?
Don't push it, little robot!
Wow, that is one hell
of an upgrade, brother!
I love being good, Dinosaur!
The Triceratops, huh? What of it?
Dinosaurs are the strongest
creatures that ever lived.
You're gonna get scrapped,
you giant tin can!
Who are you calling a tin can?
Waffle Metal never loses its luster!
It's the Tobi Rupal! No!
Little pests, where did they go?
I'm ever, ever so cross, brother dear.
Why, I just might crush that bitch's
head into a thousand little pieces.
follow him that way i'm
here what's the big hurry
damn it what is this get
this crap off me don't tire
yourself out already after
all the fun's just starting
are you a gentleman or not you
said you loved me was that a lie
i've been looking for a cute pet like
you i think i just might keep you
forever i already told you i have to
go my captain is counting on me and yet
there's women everywhere i
look ladies ladies ladies
could this be heaven i
think the man's lost his
mind yes well he's lucky
he's still good looking
of course Straw Hat and his
crew managed to break through
our forces that's no good
for kaido this is a real mess
could you hold on for a sec i don't
like you picking on my underlay
i thought a former warlord would show some
restraint but you came
out swinging like a common
thug i'll have you know
i'm the helmsman of
the Straw Hat pirates
now if you want to speak
of manners then use my
proper title my mistake
it has been a while but
i saw you when you were
a warlord so that stuck
with me you what well
enough about all that
out with it who are you
Who indeed, I do wonder.
I'll find out soon either way.
After I tear off that mask.
Not that easy, pal.
I doubt anyone will come
here, so we can hide at least.
Do you know what this is?
A statue of a dragon.
It used to be at the
entrance of the island,
but my friend broke it,
so they tossed it in here.
Your friend?
Yes.
Several years ago.
He came here in hopes
of killing my father.
That's weird.
No one's here.
Aaaaaaahhh!
Intruder alert!
I'm here for Kaido, not for you!
What now, Ace?
I got this!
You guys save the kids! On it! Good luck!
You're persistent, aren't ya?
Who the hell are you?
Tell me your name.
You tell me yours.
My name's Ace and I'm not
leaving till I take Kaido's hand.
I found them over here. Hurry.
Don't be afraid.
We came here to rescue you.
Come on.
Let's get you out of here.
You're pretty strong.
Ace!
We have the kids with us. Everyone's okay.
But the bad news is there's no
sign of Kaido anywhere here.
What?
My father is off on an expedition.
And not only him, his
officers are gone too.
Your father?
So Kaido has a daughter, and he left
her in charge of the whole place?
I am Yamato!
Now I think it's time we all
stop this pointless violence.
If you have time to wonder who I am,
get out of here right now and take
those children back to their families!
I'd be happy to do just that.
But will Kaido forgive
you for letting us go?
I have no obligation to
protect this island for him.
Ready?
We'll have you back home in no time.
Don't worry.
Your families are waiting for you.
Of course. Thank you. Thank you.
I mean it.
Are you sure you want to stay here, Ace?
We're heading back to the mainland,
so you'll be on your own for now.
It's fine.
Better to get those kids home.
I'll catch up to you guys later.
You say you're not a captain,
but there's no way someone as strong
as you would just hang around here!
Give me your worst.
You want to fight that fight?
I was bored anyway
Something's up.
If you're this strong, then why
aren't you going out to sea?
It's his fault that I'm stuck here.
Kaido.
All because I was born his child.
Oh, really?
So it's all your father's fault?
Aren't you just making excuses?
Everyone's the same.
We can't choose our parents.
You gotta make do.
Do you think I'm stupid?
You don't have to tell me that!
You say you get it, but do you?
You hate your father, but
you've given him power.
He chained your hands.
But right now, you're letting
him chain your heart, too.
Huh?
Yamato, why don't you tell
me what you really want?
I understand now.
Somewhere in my heart, I've
been holding myself back.
Before I knew it, I was
afraid to even say it.
That I want to sail the
world on a grand adventure!
That I want to be like Odin
and live my life freely!
I'll go...
to the sea.
I'll find a way off this island.
I'll find a way to be free
just like I always dreamed!
Yeah, now you're talking, Yamato.
Much better.
Did that clear things up for you?
And he came home all busted up again.
I laugh, but he really gave me a
lot of trouble when we were kids.
That little dope.
Your brother sounds like
so much fun. Hell yeah!
So, who are the top pirates right now?
Is anyone our age making a name
for themselves people our age?
Let me think well the girls are crazy
for some cabin something guy Oh, yeah.
Well, nobody is on my level just yet.
But each C has their own tough guy and one
of them just might make it big someday.
like who like who?
Kid in the south blue and law in
the north and veggie in the west.
The toughest one is gonna show up a few
years from now, and that's my brother.
You'll see.
He's going to make a big wave.
Okay, I get it.
You really love this brother of yours.
Yeah, so what?
You got a problem?
Oh, put it out!
How do you like it, you stupid jerk?
It hurts!
And as for this statue, the truth is
I'm the one who attacked it first.
But then Ace said,
Tell Kaido that this is a warning from me.
I'll be back someday to give his
real face the same treatment.
I see.
I did not know there was a pirate who
tried to save the land of Wano in the past.
My father was angry, of course.
But in the end, he never met Ace.
Oh, your father?
That means...
Oh, yeah.
Did I not tell you Kaido's my father?
Oh, no. Come on, guys.
You don't have to be afraid of me.
I hate Kaido even more than you do, I bet!
I told you I'm Odin, right?
That only fills us with more doubt!
Should I explain it again?
Kaido's my enemy, okay?
I dream of sailing on a big adventure!
I'm Odin, who only wants to be free!
Yes, sir, as you say.
We are at your mercy, mighty lord!
Stop acting like that!
We're friends, aren't we?
But wait, Yamato!
This man who tried to save the
land of Wano, where is he now?
Well...
Ace died two years ago.
You knew Ace?
I didn't see that one coming
Yeah, we were best buddies.
I've been working so hard
to become a Kunoichi.
Waiting for him to come back to see me.
But me and a loopy couldn't even
break the news to me gently.
Ace is dead now!
He just said it out of the blue.
It broke my heart to a thousand pieces.
Sorry, he can be like that sometimes.
He didn't mean to hurt you.
But you know, Otama?
Yeah, Luffy's been
through a lot of pain too.
It was tough.
Stop screwing up my party!
Yo, losers!
Pluck that turkey's wings!
Don't just stand there, kill that bozo!
Doesn't seem right.
I mean, that guy saved
our lives. Yeah, I know.
But the boss will kill us if we disobey.
Do you want me to smash your heads in?
Now get your asses in there!
To be honest, I wasn't planning
on going after Kaido myself.
Nico Robin, Mr.
Bones, do what you gotta do.
Run to the castle!
That's fine with me.
If you insist, then we're off.
You're gonna suffer, Marco!
Thought you could take all of us, huh?
You walk straight into your grave.
You guys ready?
Let's do this.
Come on now, how is that?
Fair, this is great!
You're about to face off
with an emperor, you know!
You're not nervous at all, of course, not?
What good would that do?
My captain gives the order,
and I follow as simple as that!
I'm counting on Straw Hat to
pull through and not just him!
Everyone from the worst generation.
I wonder what Ace would
have said if he knew his
brother was picking a fight
with an Emperor of the Sea.
I'm begging! Come on!
I said no!
Now drop it!
How many times do we have to go over this?
I told you who the Second Division
Commander was before you, didn't I?
And I told you why the
position was vacant.
Wano's isolationist policy played
a part in that too, we didn't know.
In other words,
since no info got in or out, it was
years before we heard Lord Odin died.
We thought about forcing our way
into Wano and starting a fight,
but there's a hundred different
ways that plan could go south.
Win or lose?
It'd take a heavy toll. You think so?
Fine!
Then why don't you let me go alone?
I made a promise.
Even Kozuki Odin couldn't defeat Kaido.
Don't overestimate yourself!
He'd crush you!
Now sit down!
Yeah, I remember how strong that Odin
guy was, but I know how you feel, Ace.
We're all searching for fame, for glory.
It's not always about that.
You don't get it, Teach.
Ace isn't looking for a prize.
Damn it.
I have to get stronger.
I have to keep my promise.
That's a heavy weight you
decided to carry, Ace.
I'm just saying.
So if Pops ever lets you go, call me.
I'd be happy to fight by your side.
You can count me in, too.
Oh, yeah?
Then we can win easy.
A little optimism is good, but come on.
Come on, Marco!
You don't really think we're just
gonna stand here and let you fly away?
Besides, all those
samurai are probably dead!
Why even bother?
Once we finish our holy son,
this fight will be over.
We will die along with the old Wind.
And from its ashes, the pirate empire
of the new Onigashima will be born!
You really think it's that easy?
You're in for a rude awakening!
Shut your trap, bird brain!
Dermot, what kind of power is that?
Is this guy invincible?
Be careful, you guys are
facing a new generation now.
The Beast Pirates will destroy
you and dominate the new era!
Ah!
Dammit!
Marco, forget these losers! Let's
go! Get ready! On three! On three!
I wasn't ready!
Wow, Luffy?
It's Ace's brother!
Um, yeah.
I thought you knew.
Like I said, he kind of sounded
cold, but he talked about his death.
But Ace is dead now.
Oh, I was the jerk.
I said all of a things to Luffy.
I wouldn't worry.
That's just Luffy being Luffy.
It'll be okay.
Yeah, but big bro!
I gotta tell him I'm sorry!
I told you not to worry, right?
Well, anyway, we should work on
that plan you came up with, Otama.
I know you got this!
Wait, so Roger had a son, and he's
Luffy's brother—that's quite the friend!
You made, yeah?
Can you believe it?
Without knowing that you brought
Luffy to Wano—indeed, we did!
Pirates are as numerous as stars
in the sky, and yet you met him.
Ace's promise will finally come true.
This can't be anything but destiny! I.
destiny I
Mean the answers in front
of us the will of D.
It's right there in Luffy's name
Ma ma ma ma
Oh, yeah! Tasty!
Nom, nom, nom, no, that's a snack!
Good.
I was so hungry, but now I'm full.
Full of raw power.
You boys enjoy your meal?
Yes, Mama.
I'm good to go.
Huh?
Well, time's a-wasting.
Straw Hats still hasn't shown up?
Here's the deal, Kaido.
Kill as many of the
Straw Hats as you like.
But Miss Nico Robin is coming with me.
Why do you need her?
Can't your three-eyed daughter
read the ancient text as well?
You mean Pudding?
I don't know.
Her true eye hasn't awakened.
She's too damn slow.
Fine.
Have it your way, then.
Humble though our strength may
be, we have held this staircase.
Proceed this way.
It shall lead Yugara to the castle roof.
Wow, thanks, Lion Viper.
It's Shishikin.
I won't forget how you helped Race.
You guys are really brave, so
promise me you'll hang in there.
Don't you worry.
I'll handle Kaido.
Now, where exactly are you
going to drop this island?
In the middle of the capital.
There's a castle there
that symbolizes the Kozuki.
You're not concerned
about all the casualties?
They're having a festival, aren't they?
That a joke?
You think slaves are that hard to come by?
The new capital will be a sight to behold.
Oh, is that where it's hidden?
The road, Poneglyph?
You're not even trying to
hide your true intentions.
Oh, get over it.
This isn't some battle of wit.
Even after all this time, you're
still like a little brother to me.
That said, let me remind you.
That day in God's Valley
when rocks came to an end,
it was me who gave you the
mythical fish fish fruit.
That's a debt you'll owe
for the rest of your life.
Say what you like.
We'll settle this after
we get our treasure.
The One Piece that is!